The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way from the moon's sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for?
And though I travel far
from where my search began,
over seas of green and shores of sand,
through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me,
someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I will search for everywhere.
Where the heck is that
rubbery, bug-eyed idiot?
This is just like him.
Didn't we all agree to be
here over 45 minutes ago?
We're gonna miss the current.
I'm sure the genius didn't even stop to
consider how the gold would weigh him down.
Why does he always insist on
making everything ten times harder?
The only schedule Luffy's
concerned with is his own.
Yeah, he's got a point there.
You don't think someone in
town beat him up, do you?
What, you mean that guy Bellamy?
Well, if Bellamy didn't beat him
up, you better believe I will!
Oh, was that right, tough girl?
Hey!
Huh?
Look there! He's back!
I knew he'd make it!
I did it, you guys!
Luffy, hurry, we're
already behind schedule.
Look, it's a Hercules!
It took me forever to find it!
You're kidding me!
Are you crazy?
Whoa, that's awesome!
Introducing the Going
Merry Flying Edition.
It can fly?
Why?!
I know!
They built it just for us!
Morons.
Something about it makes
me feel kinda uneasy.
Well, for once I agree with you.
Chickens don't even know how to fly.
They should've made it a pigeon.
What's that got to do
with anything, you dope?!
It's time to set sail!
Come on, if you're with
me, let me hear it!
Yeah!
What are you waiting for?
Get on board, unless you plan on missing
your chance at the sky, like a fool.
Thanks for the ship.
Thank them.
They built it.
Yeah, thanks for the ship, you guys.
You can have my Hercules.
Ooh, really?
You mean it?
Are you sure?
That's so kind of you.
All right, enough of this foolishness!
We don't have much time! Follow us!
We'll lead the way!
Come on, Luffy, let's go! Coming!
This city of gold is just a fairy
tale that Lion Nolan dreamt it all up!
Saruyama!
Aye!
I'm counting on you men.
I don't care what happens.
You give our friends here
everything you've got.
Time to set sail!
You heard him, shove off! Alright!
Yes, Nabi.
Well, kid, looks like this
is where we part ways.
Yep.
There's only one thing you gotta
remember above everything else. What?
Not one person in history has ever
disproved the existence of Sky Island.
Hmm.
People may say I'm crazy and even
laugh at me, but I don't care.
I'm a romantic like you romantic
So long
Oh yeah thanks for the gold
And hey don't be falling
from the sky you hear
See you around pops thanks
for everything cricket?
Think of us when you find
the City of Gold, old-timer!
Try and take it easy, okay?
Mind your own business.
It's morning already?
Burgess, see anything out there?
Can't even see an
outline of the shore yet.
You really think they're
going to that Sky Island?
Yeah,
so they say they'll be pretty
tough to follow up there,
so we gotta take care of them before that.
Okay, listen up!
It's currently 7 a .m.
We need to arrive at our final
destination no later than 11.
It's like Cricket already told us.
The spot where the knock-up stream
erupts is different every single time.
We need to get there as early as possible
in order to pinpoint its exact location.
Check it out!
It looks like we're already
running a little behind schedule.
Hey, are you knuckleheads
paying attention?
Did you see that?
It has to face forward.
I've never seen a bird quite like it.
He only faces south. Isn't that funny?
The goofy bird acts just like a compass.
Did you hear what it said?
He said he's going to
face a different direction
on purpose and laugh
at us once we're lost.
Go ahead and try.
Whoa, he's really facing north.
Told ya he couldn't do it.
Hey, show the boss some respect
and pipe down over there.
Nah, they're fine. Why?
It reminds me of the old days
when I was young and irreverent.
Uh-oh.
They say...
Hey!
There's no point getting
so worked up, Fall!
Try to relax!
And who put us behind schedule again?
You know what?
He's right.
Being tense won't get us anywhere.
We may as well enjoy ourselves.
I see your point.
Full speed ahead, men!
Anyone not relaxing answers to me!
That's better.
This is ridiculous.
Boss, look!
What's wrong?
I see the Kimulo Regalis
Cloud to the southwest!
It can't be!
What time is it?
Ten o 'clock!
They're a full hour early!
Shoujo, do you think we can make it?
Dispatch the Udon divers!
Find me those currents!
They're incredible!
What's going on now?
The cumuloregalus clouds appeared
a lot sooner than expected,
so now everyone's scrambling
to find a current!
Sonar waves detected!
There's a large current at 12 o 'clock!
Large creature detected at 9 o 'clock!
It could be a sinking!
There's wave activity detected at 10
o 'clock going against the current!
I believe it's a giant whirlpool, sir!
That's it!
Full speed ahead directly for 10 o 'clock!
That's where the knock-up stream's
gonna erupt, I'm sure of it!
Now go!
Hold on!
The waves are getting higher!
We're gonna sink!
Steady, men!
It's a pre-eruption tremor! Eruption?
Hey, Navigator!
What has the log post said?
It's pointing straight at those clouds
you mean the sky islands above that the
wind direction's perfect the clouds are
lining up exactly over the center of the
whirlpool what whirlpool i haven't seen
anything nice work brother i think we
hit the jackpot this time yes and it
seems we're in for a nice-sized explosion.
Do you think we'll make it?
Of course.
What's that?
We'll lead you to the inner edge.
All right, but what should we do?
Position yourself on the floor
and head towards the center.
Then you'll be fine.
He wants us to go to the center?
I don't remember signing up
for all this. Don't worry.
I'll make sure nothing happens to you.
I've never seen one quite this big before.
This is bad! I changed my mind!
I want to go back!
Sorry, Usopp. Too late for that.
You know who is already excited.
Let's go to the sky!
It's time for us to go.
The rest is up to you now. Good luck.
Bye, guys, and thanks
a lot for everything!
Don't go! Don't go!
I don't want to die!
Please take me with you!
Give me a break, I'm scared!
Please don't make me!
No one said anything about diving
headfirst It's into a giant whirlpool!
It's getting dark! Oh no!
I think so did!
That would be so unreasonable, Luffy!
Let's go back while we still have time!
Don't you understand the Sky Island
stuff is just a bunch of make-believe?
It's not worth getting us killed!
It's all make-believe?
Is that what you think? Usopp's right!
I think this is a really bad idea!
It may be a stupid
dream, but I have to try!
It could be our greatest adventure!
No!
Well, it's too late!
Instead of wasting your time bickering,
you all might want to take a look.
What do you mean?
It's sucking us in.
Hurry, Nami, let my arms look at you!
What happened?
It disappeared.
What's going on?
Wait, I don't get it.
Where'd it go?
I feel it.
It's starting.
The whirlpool sunk under the surface.
You don't mean.
Hold it right there.
Hey, Zoro. Huh?
Look.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't straw and loopy.
It's him.
It's that Mocktown guy.
What guy?
I've come all this way to collect
on your 100 million fairy bounty.
So don't be shy.
Were those youngsters
expecting some company?
I don't know, brother.
Huh?
Why is it getting dark out here?
100 million?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me, kid.
It says right here, Monkey D.
Luffy won it for 100 million.
And for Pirate Hunter
Zoro, 60 million Barry.
It's true.
He's got a different
poster for each of you.
Hey, Zoro, congratulations
on your new bounty.
Wait a minute, Usa.
Come on.
Do you see one for me?
Uh, no.
Look closer.
Nothing.
It looks like your bounties must have
gone way up after the Alabasta incident.
But a hundred million?
This is great! Hear that?
My bounty went up big time!
Ha, ha, 60 million's not too bad either.
It's not a good thing!
Make sure to keep your eyes
open going, Merry Crew!
It's here.
I hope they're ready for it.
Brace yourselves!
Everyone hold on or get inside!
Oh no! The ship!
It's being lifted up!
Help!
We're going to capsize!
Hold steady!
Don't let go, men!
Go, Sky Island!
What's happening we're
sailing up a huge pillar
of water this is awesome
how are we doing this?
Wind oh right i can't believe it's
finally happening let's go to Skypea!
Hold on it's not going
to be that easy look oh
what now what's wrong did
we forget about something?
The hole's starting to float.
If we don't stop it, we're
going to fall into the ocean.
What do you expect us to do about it?
We're having a hard enough
time holding on as it is.
What haven't you noticed?
Oh, no! What is that?
The Sea King.
Is that the one from before?
See?
It's only a matter of time before
the same thing happens to the Mary.
I know, but what can we do?
We don't have a whole lot of options
when it comes to Mother Nature.
We're at her mercy.
I guess we hold on and hope for the best
Spread the sails right now
Sure, it's a pillar of water,
but it's still part of the sea.
It's a rising current
The wind from below is a rising air
current produced by geothermal heat,
causing a steam explosion.
It may be packaged differently,
but it's still wind and water.
Trust me, I'm a navigator, aren't I?
Thank you, Nami!
All right, gang, Nami's leading the way!
All right, guys, catch the starboard
wind and align the ship with the current!
Yes, ma 'am!
Hey, we're ranging above
the water, is that okay?
Nami, do something!
We're gonna fall!
Come on, do it!
We're playing!
Yeah!
We're headed to the sky!
We made it there in place.
I did it! Yes.
Nami, good job!
I think I love you!
Go for it, kid.
Always remember to keep dreaming.
If the wind keeps this up, we
can sail as high as we want!
Hey, Nami!
Are we almost to Skypiea?
If it exists, it's past those clouds!
Past those clouds!
I can't wait to find out
what's up in the sky?
Let's go through them and find out!
We are We are on the cruise
We are